New York State Board of Mediation Cases 5581
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- A 2561 - A 2768 (1942). (Box 14)
  - Leser Novelty Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Italian Bakeries (group), 1942 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Roeder, Fred Mfg. Co., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Building Contractors and Mason Builders Association, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Arnold Constable, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Franklin Simon and Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Gorelick, H., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Rappaport, Louis, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Eastern Parkway Estate, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Watsky Bros., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Winston Manufacturing Co., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Chateau Martin Winery, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Manhattan Wire Goods Co., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Sussman Brothers, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Trojan Realty Corp., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Metropolitan Tool Works, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Williams R.C. and Co., Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Center Restaurants, Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - New Adelphi Hotel, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Suburban Advertising Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Cumberland Cafeteria, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Old Roumanian Restaurant, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Sally's Millinery, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Sobel Bros., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Bedford Chevrolet Sales Corp., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Franklin Simon and Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Futernick, Morris, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Hoffman Successors, Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Kreisler, J. Mfg. Sales Corp., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Dreyer Bros. Corp., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Kent Hardware Mfg. Corp., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - National Feather and Down Co., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Presto Recording Co., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Reichold Chemical Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Hanscom Baking Corp., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Union Furniture Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Werman, A. and Sons Shoe Co., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Franklin Simon and Co., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - New York Tank Barge Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Sylvian's Millinery, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Brant Chemists, Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Brant Chemists Foundation, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Carnegie Hall Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Cottage Donuts, Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - Fleischer, Philip Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Hoffman's Successors, Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - Koudelka, Emil Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - Mill End Shop, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - Superior Window Cleaning Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - Die-Craft Cutting Co., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - Famous Midwood Cafeteria, Inc., 1942 (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - Sanitary Dash Corporation, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - Schenectady Railway Company, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 89)
- A 2769 - A 2996 (1942). (Box 15)
  - Title Guarantee and Trust Co. and Lawyers Mortgage Co., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Fred's Radio Co., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Goldman and Ostrow, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Manhattan Wire Goods Co., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Sidney Siegel, Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - United Scientific Laboratories, Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Warshaw Manufacturing Co., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Bloomingdale Bros. Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Campus Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Capitol Wine and Spirit Corp., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - COE Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Crown Radio and Television Corp., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Dumont Electric Corp., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Frank Bros. Mfg. Corp., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Franklin Simon and Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Gosstex Fabrics, Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Hanscom Baking Corp., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Levine, Samuel, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - New York Central Supply Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Dowling Flyer Diner, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Luria, Max and Gelinsky, Hyman, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Pisner and Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Chalfonte Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Romanoff Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Bristol Pharmacy, Eton Chemists, Berk-Stevens, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Finkenberg, A. Sons, Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - McGregor Mfg. Co., Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Picker, M.B. Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Pohl and Salut, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Harbor Tanks Storage Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Artex-Green Corporation, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Astor Hotel Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Bell Sample Card Co., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Court-Remsen Building Corp., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Aladdin Leather Products, Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Fischer, Emil, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Paramount Macaroni Mfg. Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Shields Mfg. Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Old Roumanian, Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Lillian Dress Shop, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Golden Brand Nut Products, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Arley Management Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Magonigle Trucking Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Sobel Bros., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - National Shoe Stores, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Metro Sacks Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - The Namm Store, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - American Addressing Machine Corp., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Doyle, T.S. Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Hotel Belvedere, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Krasne, A. Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Green-wood Cemetery, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Kessler Reliable Silk Store, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - P.A. Trucking Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Universal Camera Corp., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Krasne Bros. (Independent Truckmen of), 1942 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Engelhard, Charles Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Laboratory Furniture Co., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Lilienfeld, Mollye, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Nedick Stores, Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Quaker Sugar Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Abrams, Morris Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Royal Card and Paper Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Savoy Brass Mfg. Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Spaghetti Spot Restaurant, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Anchor Motor Freight Corp., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Nathor Coffee Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Sherard Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Jules Millinery, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Corona Insulated Wire Co., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Pola Millinery, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Duroyd Gasket and Die Mfg. Co., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Leonard's Catering, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Purity Bakeries Corp., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Rutledge Associates, inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Sixth Hotel Corporation, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Circle Construction Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Schenley Corp., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Childs Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - New Yorker delicatessen Stores, Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Le Roy Metal Bed Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Standard Coated Products Corp., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Zaharoff, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Caton Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Danny's Shoe Repair, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Eagle Electric Mfg. Co., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Savarise, M., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Enterprise Tinware Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - Childs Company, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Loft Candy corp., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 90)
- A 3001 - A 3287 (1942). (Box 16)
  - Big Four Merchandise, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Consumers Cooperative Services, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Arco Metal Craft Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Atlas Sturdy Products Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Bonwit Teller, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Crawford Clothes Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Gobel, Adolf Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Master Tool and Die Makers, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Topps Hosiery, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Tashman, Harry F., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Greater New York Photo Finishers Association, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Kern, George and Son Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - 325 West 118th Street, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Kuflik, A.J., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Shipman Stationery, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Kent Paper, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Teich, L. and Sons, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Goodwear Shoe Repair System, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - The Flower Box, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Unique Balance Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Dewey Square Hotel, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Gerstenzang, Abraham Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Krasne, A. Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Sterling Battery Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Atlantic Baking Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Shield Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - West End Printing Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Barry, E.J. Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Childs and Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Hydromantic Machine Corp., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Champion Shoe Mfg. Corp., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Fibre Yarn Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Finkenberg's, A. Sons, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Huber, J.M. Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Ledkote Products Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Liquidometer Corporation, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Shein's Department Store, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Sanitary Dash Corporation, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Spear and Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Wearbest Footwear Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Ronzoni Macaroni Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Waksman, Lewis, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Limited Editions Club, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Briam Manufacturing Corp., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Downtown Dry Goods Jobbers Assn., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - International Salt Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Kent Hardware Mfg. Corp., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Premier Sample Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Art Steel Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Baker Brush Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Brightman Leather Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Brout Credit Jewelers, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Doyle, T.S. Company Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Fastenberg, I., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Handi-man Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Hochhauser, S. Trucking, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Lowe, Joe Corporation, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Spear and Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Atlantic Baking Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Bruno of Hollywood, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Brooklyn Union Gas Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Champion Shoe Corp., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Continental Oil Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Karlick's Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Lynn Pharmacy, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Olympia Baking Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Pocker, Jacob, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Rosenbluth Bros., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Abbott Baking Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Stenola Products Corporation, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Appleton, Wolf, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - 1942 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Walters Radio and Television Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Consolidated Film Industries, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Dosik Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Greenberg Bros. Children's Stores, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Paper Box Credit Bureau, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Rubin, Irwin, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Ward Baking Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Bogen, David and Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Cambridge Straps, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Egeronkov, V. and Sons, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Famous Envelope Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Feuer Transportation Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Moriarty and Johnson Leather Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Optical Research Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Queens Machine Corporation, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Reader Mail, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - St. Vincent's Chemists, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Seal-o-Strain Corporation, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - Spear and Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - True-Value Slipper and Sandal Corp., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - Cameo Beauty Departments, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 93)
  - Goldfarb, M. - My Florist, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - Card Crafts, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - Elk Grove Wines, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - Rutledge Associates, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 97)
  - Scall Undergarment Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 98)
  - Metropolitan Tobacco Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 99)
  - French Powder Puff Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 100)
  - Gimbel Brothers, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 101)
  - Shein, S. Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 102)
  - Lowe, Joe Corporation, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 103)
  - Rite Radio Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 104)
  - Romeike, Henry Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 105)
  - Wilsonia Apartments, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 106)
  - Corrigan Casket Company, John E., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 107)
  - Huyler's, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 108)
  - Niemand Brothers, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - United Parcel Services, Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 110)
  - Winston Mfg. Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 111)
  - Keller-Dorian Paper Company, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 112)
  - Art Novelty Doll Shoe Co., Inc., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 113)
  - General Quilting Mfg. Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 114)
  - Orchard Meat Market (Dannenberg and Kantor), 1942 (Box 16, Folder 115)
  - Hadassah, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 116)
  - Imperial Metal and Stamping Corp., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 117)
  - Schwartz, G.N., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 118)
  - Abbott Baking Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 119)
- A 3288 - A 3523 (1942). (Box 17)
  - G. and M. Pastry Shop, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Keynote Recordings, Inc. Music Room, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Leon and Eddie, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Metro Jewelry Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Renart Sportswear Corp., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Irving Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Standard Furniture Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Varick Machine and Tool Works, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Willor Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Yorkville Master Barbers Assn, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Independent Quilting Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Jones, Daniel Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Quilter's Association of N.Y., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Mackay Radio Company, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Ocon Brothers, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Dorset Foods, Ltd., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Harris, M.H. Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Clarostat Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Florin Realty Corp., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Frankel Window Cleaning Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Manhattan Window Cleaning Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Arrowhead Sewing Machine Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Thomas S.B. Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Greater N.Y. Retail Furnishings and Dry Goods Association, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Greenwood Cemetery, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Kelton Cosmetic Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Lignum Chemical Works, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Madison House, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Par-Metal Products Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - United Parcel Service of New York, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Clarostat Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Dumont Electric Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Gimbel Brothers, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Hanman Wiping Materials Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Kirchberger and Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Modern Wood Products Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Spear and Company, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Weiner, Irving, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Weldt's Bakery, Edward, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Klenoff Corp. Henry and Jacob, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Magnus, Alice, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Eisman, Frank, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Childs Company, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Excellent Sample Card House, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Laggett, Francis H. and Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Plymouth Rock Provision Co., Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - S. and W. Fine Foods, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - European Style Candy Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - General Baking Company, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Great Western Beef Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Klein Piano Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - La Bella Palermo Bakery, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Munsell, Eugene Company, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Paper Box Credit Bureau, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - S. and S. Curtain and Drapery Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Sanitary Dash Corporation, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Tiffany Linen Shop, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Wilsonia Apartments, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Plaza Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Accurate Shoe Corp., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Central Wire Frame Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Court Degraw Theatre, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - De Lisser Machine and Tool Corp., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Hilton Tool and Machine Corp., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Serveall Paper Box Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Superior Diner, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - United Parcel Service, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Yorktown Shoe Repair, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Bloomingdale's, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Kings County Lighting Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Schacter, Jacob, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Airwing Products, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Allied Basket Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Brant Chemists, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Cahn and Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Courtade, J.N. and Sons, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Decorative Cabinet Corp., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Kaplan, Joseph A. Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Parke Davis and Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Rose Frame and Mirror Works Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Carol Textile, Sussman Bros., Max Feinberg, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Associated Bedding Manufacturers of Greater New York, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Bliss, E.W. Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - Eichen Cigar Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - Hotel Pharmacy, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - Jaffe, Philip, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Kress Quality Laundry, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Reliable Contracting Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - Ware, Howard R. Corp, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - Artex-Green Corp., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Browning Precision Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Eveready Hardware Mfg. Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - Fifty-Five West 110th Street, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Hostess Cake Company, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - Kittay, B. and Sons, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Luxor Baths, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - Roth and Zweiman, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - Towers Pharmacy, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - A.R.S. Realty Corporation, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - Duroyd Gasket and Die Manufacturing Co., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 100)
  - Fitzgerald, E.P., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 101)
  - Imperial Steel Partition Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 102)
  - Industrial Wrecking Co. Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - Ledkote Products Co. of New York, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 104)
  - Martha Washington Hotel, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 105)
  - Reader Mail, Inc., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 106)
- A 3524 - A 3771 (1943). (Box 18)
  - Reber, John and Bros. French Pastry Corp., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Universal Metal Products Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Belove Watchcase Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Freezing and Cold Storage Corp., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Chambord Restaurant, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Famous Dairy Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Feiner, P. and Sons, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Grennan Bakeries, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Sherry Stores, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - United Master Barbers Association, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Gerstenzang, Abraham Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Greater New York Wrecking, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Shoe Manufacturing Board of Trade, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - New York and Brooklyn Casket Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Emkay Watch Hand Company, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Old Dutch Mustard Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Rowe Cigarette Service Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Spear and Company, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Amalgamated Housing Corp., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Boro-Progressive Master Barbers, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Buda, Marcus and Son, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - General Arc Lighting Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Quigan, Frank J. Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Garment Box Assn. of New York, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Union Equities, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Schecter and Knoph, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Kluge's Bakery, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - One Plaza Street, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Spear and Company, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Penzel Mueller and Co. Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Feldman, S. Lumber Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Putterman Footwear Corp., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Rand Tea and Coffee Stores, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Sparag, Edith Studios, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Universal Camera Corp., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Comet Metal Products Company, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Lincoln and Ulmer, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - New York Meat Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Reiner, Ben, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Whitehall Chemists, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Ward Baking Company, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Pathe Engineering and Tool Manufacturing Division, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Ludwig Baumann and Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Savoy Brass Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Ward Baking Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Panoramic Radio Corporation, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Paramount Silk House, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Spear and Company, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Thomas, S.B. Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Universal Brass Turning Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Allied Cleaning Contractors Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - G.M. Co. Mfg. Company, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - White Oak Shoe Repair, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Prentiss, R.J. and Company, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Fifth Avenue Tea Room, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Mail Advertising Service Assn, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Thomas, S.B. Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Canada Dry Ginger Ale, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Minkin, David, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - City Provision Company, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Wearbest Footwear, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Friedel Bros. Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Stern and Kreshover, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Metro Sacks Company, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Max Posnick Co., Inc., and Wood Furniture Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Royal Homecraft Corp., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - United Parcel Service, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Bloom, M. and Sons, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - The Flower Box, Inc., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Leader Novelty Candy Co., 1943 (Box 18, Folder 70)